You don't have javascript enabled. Good luck with that.

[](javascript:void(0))

https://www.peeplookup.com/

Privacy Policy
==============

Updated 3rd October 2018

BY USING THIS WEB SITE AND PROVIDING PERSONAL INFORMATION TO peeplookup.com YOU CONSENT TO THE COLLECTION, USE AND DISCLOSURE OF THAT INFORMATION IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

General
-------

Please review the Terms of Use in.comjunction with this Privacy Policy. All capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy may have the meanings given to them in the Terms of Use. The information that users provide via this Web Site, together with information regarding the manner in which the user uses this Web site, will not be processed or disclosed by peeplookup.com except as may be permitted by the Terms of Use or this Privacy Policy. By being a user of this Web site, the user agrees that peeplookup.com may share with other parties aggregate, individual, and locator information gathered by peeplookup.com in the.comrse of the user's.comtinuing individual use of this Web site.

* "Aggregate information" is information that describes the habits, usage patterns and/or demographics of users as a group but does not describe or reveal the identity of any particular user.
* "Individual information" is information about a user that is presented in a form distinguishable from of information relating to other users but not in a form that personally identifies any user or enables the recipient to.comunicate directly with any user.
* "Locator information".comsists of a user's name, e-mail address, physical address and/or other data about the user that enables the recipient to personally identify the user. Any user who does not wish to receive any special offers or.comunications from peeplookup.com directly or on behalf of suppliers, may so notify peeplookup.com at the address listed below. (Note that a user's election not to receive such information will not affect the user's receipt of offers and.comunications that were processed prior to the users' election.) Locator information and individual information may be processed and stored by peeplookup.com Users may.comtact peeplookup.com to determine whether such information has been accurately r.comded and, if not, to request.comrection of any inaccuracies in the information r.comded by peeplookup.com

The information.comlected is used to improve the.comtent of our Web pages and the quality of our service, and is not shared with or sold to other organizations for.comercial purposes, except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

a) It is necessary to share or disclose information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding unlawful activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law.

b) peeplookup.com transfers information about you if peeplookup.com is acquired by or merged with another.comany. In this event, peeplookup.com will notify you before information about you is transferred and b.coms subject to a different privacy policy.

c) It is necessary to provide information to our independent.comtractors who host and maintain the Web Site and e-mail services, and other service providers and suppliers if the disclosure will enable that party to perform business, professional or technical support to peeplookup.com

2\. Information Gathering and Usage
-----------------------------------

When you register for peeplookup.com or use peeplookup.com we may ask for information such as your name, email address,.comany name and address information. peeplookup.com uses.comlected information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement,.comtact, and research.

3\. Cookies
-----------

A.comkie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's.comuters and stored on your.comuter's hard drive. Cookies are required to use the peeplookup.com service. peeplookup.com uses.comkies to r.comd current session information and may use permanent.comkies. You are required to log-in to your peeplookup.com application site after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you against others accidentally accessing your a.comnt.comtents.

4\. Data Storage
----------------

peeplookup.com uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run the peeplookup.com web site. Although peeplookup.com owns the.come, databases, and all rights to the peeplookup.com application, you retain all rights to your data.

5\. Changes
-----------

peeplookup.com may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your peeplookup.com a.comnt or by placing a prominent notice on the web site. "peeplookup.com may modify, alter, or update this Privacy Policy at any time. User's and a.comnt holders are responsible for reviewing this web page frequently to ensure they are aware of any changes."

Questions
---------

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be sent to [hello@peeplookup.com](mailto:hello@peeplookup.com)

PeepLookup

© peeplookup.com 2024

Please share us. It will help us support this site.

[](javascript:void(0))
